{
    "subject": "resource/Forces'_Sweetheart_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Forces' Sweetheart (film) is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867379069328308,
            "question": "Is 'Forces' Sweetheart' considered a type of movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9531949162483215,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Forces' Sweetheart'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7941831350326538,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Forces' Sweetheart'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7678371667861938,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of another film in the same genre as 'Forces' Sweetheart'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6258910298347473,
            "question": "Where was 'Forces' Sweetheart' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4711649715900421,
            "question": "When was 'Forces' Sweetheart' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40486451983451843,
            "question": "What is the overall theme explored in 'Forces' Sweetheart'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2838379740715027,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors or directors associated with films of this type?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24751032888889313,
            "question": "Did 'Forces' Sweetheart' receive any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2010766714811325,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of films within this genre?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Forces' Sweetheart (film) is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8314_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did 'Forces' Sweetheart' receive any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8314_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors or directors associated with films of this type?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8314_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall theme explored in 'Forces' Sweetheart'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8314_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8314_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of whether the statement \"Forces' Sweetheart (film) is a type of Film\" is supported by the documents:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8314/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt mentions that \"Forces' Sweetheart was also a 1953 film.\" This directly supports the statement that Forces' Sweetheart (film) is a type of Film.\n\nNote: The other files mentioned in the context information do not provide any additional relevant information to contradict or support the given statement. Therefore, based on the provided documents, the statement \"Forces' Sweetheart (film) is a type of Film\" is supported."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about \"Forces' Sweetheart\" being mentioned as both a title given to entertainment women in the British Armed Forces and as a film from 1953. Therefore, it can be reasonably concluded that \"Forces' Sweetheart (film)\" is indeed of the type \"Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}